Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Where are you going?
We're not finished.
He failed to kill Jaffrey. It's over.
It can still work.
No. it can't.
We'll never get another chance.
We need to get out of the country.
You really want another body
to get rid of?
- Put the gun down.
- I'll drop you too.
- Gimball's dead.
- How did he die?
This country is fucking mad.
Who cares how it happened.
It'll have the same impact.
It can still work.
We'll succeed…
…if we're all in.
I've always been in.
I wasn't the one who fucked up.
What?
Don't think that because your father
was my captain
and we broke bread together.
it will stop me from pulling the trigger.
Fuck me. guys.
This is crazy.
This is what we're supposed
to be doing to the British.
Walk away from me again
and I'll put a bullet
in the back of your skull.
Now let's blind them.
Success?
First desk was blinded.
The rest of the Park was blinded.
Now for the final step.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm